(忆往昔)
我们给你介绍记录者
Let us introduce you to the men of letters.
一个道貌岸然的激进行善组织
It's a rabid group of sanctimonious do-gooders.
是个神秘团体
It's a secret society.
这个颠三倒四的世界中
The last true beacon of light
最后一座真正的灯塔
in a world gone topsy-turvy.
欧洲团体  他们在二战期间有行动
European team-- they were active during world war ii.
1939年加入
Inducted in 1939,
是被派往欧洲的一小支代表团的一员
part of a small delegation that was sent to Europe.
我们是传人
We're legacies.
时光旅行  那是合理的计划吗
Time travel? That's a reasonable plan?
怎么  天使得到时空旅行车了吗
What, angels got their hands on some Deloreans?
我是怎么来的
How did I get here?
你借用灵魂之力才到这儿的
You tapped the power of your soul to get here?
该死的穿越时空
Freaking time travel, man.
修黎社  都是纳粹
The Thule society. Right. They were Nazis.
-纳粹巫师  -黑魔法
- Nazi necromancers. - Dark magic,
大多是用在死人身上的
mostly with dead people.
你可以杀我  但你们杀不尽修黎社
You can kill me, but you will never kill all the Thule.
混账纳粹
Nazi bastards.
路西法
Lucifer.
该死的
Bloody hell.
我们聊聊吧
Let's chat.
我们想要杀死黑暗
We want to kill the darkness.
我们必须杀死黑暗
We need to kill the darkness.
我有两次杀阿玛拉的机会
I've had two shots at Amara.
但我觉得我做不到
And I don't think I can.
我明白  迪恩
I got it, Dean.
(1943年  纳粹占领的法国)
(盖世太保总部)
已经到了
It has arrived.
是的  我叫了军队护送
Yes, I have ordered a full military escort.
不用说
Naturally...
我会把文物给您送去的
...I will bring the artifact to you.
别这样
Please...
这是我莫大的荣幸
...it is my great honor.
元首
Mein fuhrer.
床都凉了
The bed is cold.
亲爱的
Liebchen.
那是什么  我的爱人
What is that, mon amour?
这是我来此的目的
This is why I've come here.
我还以为你占领我的国家是为了认识我呢
And I thought you occupied my country to meet me.
你是额外的好处  黛尔芬
You were a bonus, Delphine.
是件珍宝
A treasure.
我的小同谋
Ma petite collaboratrice.
但这个
But this...
这是我的国家一直在等的东西
this is what my country has been waiting for.
我能看看吗
Can I see it?
不乖哦  黛尔芬
Naughty Delphine.
求你了
Bitte.
就看一眼
One little peek.
那么  是真的
So, it's true.
亲爱的
Mein liebchen.
我这辈子过得一直不易  但这几个月
I have lived a hard life. But these months?
假装喜欢你这样的纳粹猪  简直最糟了
Pretending to love a Nazi Cochon like you has been the worst.
但这一刻
But this moment...
看着你死掉
watching you die?
是最棒的
It is the best.
记录者向你致意
The Men of Letters send their regards.
[邪恶力量 第11季第14集]
没咖啡了
We're out.
昨天还有半包呢
There was a half a bag yesterday.
我都喝了
I killed it.
你知道纳粹有个专门进行考古的分支吗
Did you know the Nazis had a special branch devoted to archaeology?
这么早就考纳粹常识  还没有咖啡因作伴
A little early for Nazi trivia, especially without caffeine.
他们叫做"圣遗物"
It was called, uh, the "AhnenErbe."
在德国境内到处有分支
There were sites all over Germany,
随着纳粹领土不断扩张
and then as the Nazis increased their territory,
他们相继出现在波兰
they started popping up in... in Poland,
芬兰  北非
Finland, uh, North Africa.
这为什么会比我们没有咖啡更严重
Yeah, how is this more important than our coffee situation?
因为我有发现
'cause I found something.
我们需要点东西...魔法
I mean, we need something... magic,
一件足以抵抗阿玛拉的武器
a-a weapon strong enough to give us a shot against Amara.
所以我一直在翻查历史
So I've been looking outside the lore in history,
我发现了这个  "维希备忘录"
and I found this... uh, "The Vichy memorandums."
这些纳粹的通信
They were Nazi communications
直至今日仍让史学家不解
that puzzle historians to this day,
里面提到了一件圣遗物
and they speak of a superweapon obtained
得到的超能武器
by the AhnenErbe,
据说其威力足以赢下战争
said to be strong enough to win the war.
是吗  是什么
Yeah? What was it?
备忘录中  称其为
Well, uh, these memos refer to it as...
"上帝之手"
"The Hand of God."
这算是一个概括的统称
I mean, that was sort of a catchall term
指多件他在圣经时期在人间碰触过的物件
for several objects he touched on earth in biblical times,
但据信这些东西还残留了他的法力
but they're believed to contain traces of his power.
纳粹信的事多了
Yeah, well, the Nazis believed a lot of things.
迪恩  路西法被关在笼子里
Dean, Lucifer's caged.
上帝不见人影
God's M.I.A.
有能力与阿玛拉抗衡的生灵都不在
The only beings strong enough to battle Amara are gone.
如果我们要对抗她  有什么武器
If we're gonna fight her, what better way to arm up
比他残留的法力更好呢
than with an actual dose of his power?
好吧  那么你是说纳粹拿到了
Okay, so you said the Nazis got their hands on
这些"手"之一
one of these, uh..."hands."
-嗯  -如果这东西强大到能帮他们赢得战争
- Right. - Well, if it was so powerful it could win them the war,
-那他们怎么还输了  -因为东西失窃了
- why didn't it? - Because they lost it.
在送去柏林的路上被盗了
En route to Berlin, it was stolen.
纳粹天上地下地找那个贼
The Nazis searched high and low for the thief,
但主嫌犯一直未被找到
but they never found their prime suspect.
这里  黛尔芬·赛杜尔
Uh, here. Delphine Seydoux.
一位纳粹高官的法国情妇
French mistress to a high-ranking Nazi.
本以为她是个法奸
Thought to be a French traitor
直到她杀了她的德国情人  偷走了武器
till she killed her German lover and made off with the weapon.
盟军的间谍  法国抵抗组织
Allied spy? French resistance?
纳粹也是这么想的
That's what the Nazis thought,
但他们的调查得出了另一种结论
But their investigation led them to a different conclusion...
她是位"女记录者"
That she was "Un femme de lettres."
女记录者
A WoMan of Letters.
长官
Uh, sir?
您想听听最新的灵魂数报告吗
Would you like to hear the latest soul numbers?
不要  我不在乎
No, because I don't care.
那么关于阿玛拉的最新情况呢
How about an update on Amara?
最新情况就是
Well, the update is...
没有新情况  我们还没找到她
well, that there is no update. We still haven't found her.
长官  容我说一句
Sir, if I may...
鉴于您现在登基了  我们需要点指示
Since you've claimed the throne, we could use some direction.
任何指示都好
Any direction.
我们可以调派人力
We could deploy a force.
去地面上到处找她
Real boots on the ground, shake the trees to find her.
当然是由您来带领
W-with you leading the charge, of course.
太久以来  掌舵之人懦弱低能
We have had a coward and a fool at the helm for too long.
或许现在...
Perhaps it's time to...
狗狗有话要说
Doggie wants to speak.
你好大胆
How dare you.
这么厚颜无耻
The impudence.
毫无谦逊
The lack of humility.
哪能这么跟主子说话
That's no way to talk to your master...
路西法
Lucifer.
好狗狗
That's a good doggie.
谁知道记录者还有欧洲分舵
Who knew the Men of Letters had European chapters?
或许并没有完整的分支机构
Maybe it wasn't an entire chapter.
只是有些人手
Just some assets, you know?
嗯  40年代就让女人加入
Yeah, and letting women join way back in the '40s?
我从来没觉得
I just never got the impression
他们那么重视性别平等
that they were so big on gender equality.
从名字就看得出啊
You know, it's right there in the name.
那是二战
Well, it was World War II.
是全员出动的情况啊
Kind of an all-hands-on-deck situation, you know?
是啊  铆工露斯(二战美国女工代表形象)
Yeah, Rosie the Riveter.
-真酷  -找到了
- Cool. - Here you go.
这份报告是由克利福德·亨肖所写
This report was written by Clifford Henshaw,
一位1943年的驻地堡记录者
a bunker-based Man of Letters, back in 1943.
时代对的上
It's the right era.
但是法文的
But it's in French.
怎么样
Well?
绝对是讲黛尔芬的
So it's definitely about Delphine.
每页最上面都有她的名字
Her name's at the top of every page.
看啊
And check this out.
克利福德和黛尔芬
They're transcriptions from transAtlantic cables
跨大西洋电报的副本
between Clifford and Delphine.
-他们说了什么  -给我点时间
- What do they say? - Uh, give me a second.
网络翻译有点问题
Web translation's kind of buggy.
不是吧
Seriously?
哥们  这才中午
Dude, it's, like, noon.
你把咖啡都喝光了
Uh, well, you drank all the coffee,
那你让我喝什么  水吗
so what am I supposed to drink? Water?
看啊
Look at this.
他们在安排
They were making arrangements
把文物送出欧洲进行保护
to get the artifact out of Europe to keep it safe.
亨肖找了一个战略情报局的
Uh, Henshaw pulled some strings
记录者帮忙
with a Man of Letters in the O.S.S.
请求征用一艘在役美国潜水艇
To requisition an active U.S. submarine to transport
运送黛尔芬和武器回到美国
Delphine and the weapon back to the states.
回到这儿来
Back to here.
-到地堡来吗  -是的
- Wait, the bunker? - Yeah.
那么武器一直在这里
So it's been here the whole time?
不对
No.
没送到
Never arrived.
美国蓝鳍号在跨大西洋航行途中
Uh, the U.S.S. Bluefin came under German attack
遭德国攻击
midway through its trip across the Atlantic.
潜水艇沉没了
The sub was sunk.
直至今日  潜艇和里面的东西都尚未被打捞上来
The ship and its contents haven't been recovered to this day.
这可好  东西没了
Great. It's lost.
真是这样吗
Or is it?
我看是的
Well, yeah, I'd say so.
海潮卷走了残骸
I mean, tides took the wreckage.
多年来一直有潜水器企图搜寻
Submersibles have been trying to locate it for years.
如果詹姆斯·卡梅隆花重金都
I mean, if James Cameron and his "Avatar" billions
-找不到  那...  -是啊  但是
- can't find it... - Yeah, but...
我们有詹姆斯·卡梅隆没有的东西
We have something that James Cameron doesn't have.
就这些了吗
That's all of it?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
按要求从您地穴拿来武器
The requested weaponry from your crypts.
您...满意吗
Does it...please you?
省省吧
Spare me.
你的伤怎么样了  狗狗
How are your wounds, doggie?
我...
They are...
是罪有应得
no less than I deserve.
你怕你的主子
You're scared of your master.
乖狗狗
That's a good doggie.
但这是装相
But it's an act.
我虽然打败了你  但
I broke you, but, um...
没错  我还能闻到
Yep, I can still smell it.
你有一股美妙的挑衅之气
You've got that delectable little whiff of defiance.
你是在演戏吧
You're just playing, huh?
静待机会  重夺王位
Waiting for your moment to retake the throne.
我说得对吧
Am I right?
是  长官
Yes, sir.
那好吧  告诉我
Well, then... Tell me, uh,
曾经和未来的地狱之王
once and future... King of Hell,
你一直在观察我的统治
you've been watching my rule.
你的小脑瓜里
What treasonous thoughts do you have
琢磨什么叛逆的念头呢
brewing in that little head of yours, huh?
你究竟在想什么
What are you really thinking?
实话吗  长官
The truth, sir?
是的
Yeah.
你不够强大
You're not strong enough.
你的武器被送来了
You've had your weapons delivered.
但你意识到  这不够
You realize they won't be enough.
如果你觉得你能打败阿玛拉
If you thought you could beat Amara,
你就会主动去找她
you'd be taking the fight to her,
现在就会去了
right now.
你真是只聪明的狗狗
You're a clever little doggie.
你说得对  我现在或许有些准备不足
You're right. At the moment, I-I may be a bit underequipped.
或许击败阿玛拉与我跟一些人说的那样不同
Maybe defeating Amara was a bit more of a team effort
的确需要团队合作
than I led certain people to believe.
虽说如此
You know, all that said...
我还是你的主人
I'm still your master.
我是不是把你从狗舍里放出来太早了
Did I let you out of that kennel too soon?
不是
No.
不许乱吠
No barking.
好戏开始了
It's showtime.
你好啊  迪恩
Hello, Dean.
上帝碰过的东西有好几样
There were several god-touched objects,
但我从未想过有任何一件没被大水毁掉
but it never occurred to me that any had survived the flood,
更别提20世纪了
let alone the 20th century.
你觉得我们可以用它对付阿玛拉吗
Do you think we can use it against Amara?
太完美了
It's perfect.
我可以送你们回去
I can get you back there.
你没有翅膀啊
Without wings?
小卡  你都不能瞬移
Cass, you can't even teleport.
时间旅行  是另一套系统
Time travel's is a... it's a whole different system.
我说的吧
Told ya.
那么  这是最后坐标吗
So, uh, these the last coordinates?
那是蓝鳍号最后向陆地发出的信号  是的
That's the Bluefin's last transmission to shore, yeah.
-好吧  -等等
- All right. - Wait a second.
小卡  时间旅行不是有危险的吗
Cass, aren't there still risks with time travel?
难道没有什么后果...
I mean, aren't there consequences that...
萨姆
Sam...
-这是最理想的情况  -什么
- This is the ideal scenario. - What?
那艘潜艇是浮在海洋里的一个锡罐子
That sub's a tin can floating in the middle of the ocean,
而且注定要沉没
doomed to go down.
在海底两万里怎么也破坏不了历史
You can't really mess with history at 20,000 leagues.
我们进去  拿到武器  就出来
So we get in, get the weapon, get out.
毫无危险
It's a milk run.
这不是个很好的计划啊
Well, t-that's not a-a very good plan.
如果出了问题
Well, if things get out of hand,
那小卡把我弄回来就成
then Cass'll just zap me right back.
你
You?
你不能去
You're not going.
什么
I beg your pardon?
-你得留下  -留下
- You need to stay here. - Stay here?
以防出什么闪失
Just in case things go sideways,
得有人留下
somebody needs to be left standing
去对付黑暗
to take care of the Darkness.
我们不能都去冒险
We can't risk us both,
现在  我是最没价值的选手
and at the moment, I'm the least valuable player.
你们都知道我对阿玛拉下不去手
You both know that I can't kill Amara,
所以我至少可以
so the least I could do
去拿到我们需要的东西  好让你杀了她
is get the thing that we need so that you can.
那么你要我闲坐在这里
So you expect me to sit here and ride the pine
等着你和小卡去扮儒勒·凡尔纳
while you and Cass go play Jules Verne?
没错  不对  谁啊
Yes. No. Uh, who?
我会盯紧他的
I won't let him out of my sight.
你会一直陪着他
You'll stay by his side the entire time?
是的
I will.
萨姆
Sam...
让我去吧
Let me do this.
好吗  我需要这么做
Okay? I need to do this.
-小心点  -我什么时候不小心了
- Be safe. - When am I not?
我们走吧  小卡
Let's do this, Cass.
一路顺风
Bon voyage.
小卡
Cass?
我参军是为了击沉德国军舰
See, I enlisted to sink German ships.
该你了
You're up.
起来  假期结束了
Let's go. Vacation's over.
我们在海湾巡逻什么行动都碰不上
Now we got zip running patrols in the bay.
艇长现在又带我们走别的路
Now captain's got us going the wrong direction?
就为帮个女人执行神秘任务
To run some mystery mission for some broad?
什么道理啊
Tell me how that makes sense.
别想了  休息一下吧
I wouldn't worry about it. Get some rest.
你知道我休息不了
You know I can't rest.
小卡
Cass?
怎么...
Why...
等等  迪恩呢
Wait a second. Where's Dean?
我们跳了
We made the leap.
他上去了  我没有
He got on. I didn't.
什么
What?
我没能进入艇体
I couldn't make it past the hull.
1996年
1996?
黛尔芬呢
Where's Delphine?
那女人呢
Where's the broad?
我不知道你在说什么
I-I-I don't know what you're talking about.
肯定是有人给潜艇加了防护咒
Someone must have warded the ship.
黛尔芬  肯定是她
Delphine. It has to be.
她是想保护武器  是吧
I mean, she's protecting the weapon, right?
小卡
Cass.
回到她登艇前的最后一个港口啊
Just go back to their last port before she boarded,
留个讯息让迪恩知道情况
leave a message so Dean knows.
留在哪
Where?
留在哪能让迪恩看到又不被艇员看到
Where would Dean see it that the crew wouldn't?
他发现防护咒的几率
He's as likely to find the warding
跟发现我留下的消息的几率一样大
as he is any message I'd leave.
那就送我去  你把迪恩送进艇体了
Then send me. You got Dean past the hull.
嗯
Right.
然后再钻一次已经坑过我们的陷阱
We'll double-down on what screwed us the first time.
你今天的点子真是棒极了
You're really bringing your "A" ideas today.
我居然弄丢了它
I can't believe I lost it.
他
Him.
我居然弄丢了迪恩
Can't believe I lost Dean.
现在只能靠他找到并清理掉防护咒
Well, it's up to him now to find and clear the warding.
不  我们可以帮忙
No. We can help.
法术或天使传说里肯定有什么能用上
There's got to be something in... in... in magic or angel lore.
能从外面去掉魔咒
You know, some way to clear the sigils from the outside.
小卡
Cass...
别担心  我们会把他弄回来的
Don't worry. We'll bring him back.
小心  过人了
Look out. Coming through.
过人了
Coming through.
长官
Sir.
我什么时候能抽烟
When can I smoke?
等轮到你了  我会告诉你的
When it's your turn, I'll let you know.
你们肯定有人在机舱里休息吧
Surely some of you boys take breaks in the engine room?
艇长要你别乱走动
Captain wants you stayed put.
我猜猜  他担心我会分他手下的心
Let me guess. He fears I would distract his men?
不希望女人在艇上乱跑
Does not want a skirt roaming the decks?
给我个火
Give me the light.
女士
But, ma'am, uh...
你穿着裤子呢
you're wearing pants.
真是的
Rich, ain't it?
像示巴女王一样往那儿一坐
Frog's sittin' pretty like Queen of Sheba,
在军官室里享受客房服务
getting room service in the wardroom,
我还不能抱怨  你看见那妞儿了吗
and I can't even gripe 'cause... Well, you seen that dame?
看她那对儿长腿
The gams on her?
是啊  她真漂亮
Yeah. Yeah, she's a hottie.
那对儿长腿啊
Yeah, those gams, huh?
你是谁
Who are you?
黛尔芬
Delphine...
你可能会觉得难以置信  但
You might find this hard to believe, but...
这艇上没人知道我的名字
Not a soul on this ship knows my name,
我再问一遍  你是谁
so I repeat, who are you?
借过
Coming through!
我是克利福德·亨肖的朋友
I'm a friend of Clifford Henshaw.
我是记录者
I'm a Man of Letters.
就是他
That's him.
就是他  艇长
That's the guy. Captain.
-坐下  -好吧  我
- Sit down. - Okay, I'm...
他抢了我的衣服
He took my clothes,
还把我五花大绑
and he hog-tied me in the head, this guy.
-我们拿他怎么办  艇长  -搜身
- What should we do with him, captain? - Search him.
好了  好了
All right, all right.
这...
That's...
彼得  这是你的吗
Petey, this yours?
(无信号)
这是什么
What the hell is this?
电话
It's a phone.
是啊  能揣在兜里的电话
Right. A phone in your pocket.
他接下来要跟我们说
Next thing this guy's gonna tell us
-他是从外太空来的  -是啊  或者未来
- is he's from space. - Yeah, or the future.
我就是
I-I am.
詹姆斯·迪尔伯恩艇长
Captain James Dearborn?
我叫迪恩·温彻斯特
My name is Dean Winchester,
我的确来自未来  前来执行任务
and I am on a mission from the future,
细节我无权透露
the details of which I am not at liberty to discuss.
但不到一小时内
But know this... within the hour,
一艘德国驱逐舰就将发现并袭击这艘潜艇
a German destroyer will find and attack this submarine,
你们会沉没
and you will go down.
好吧  你要说的说了
Okay, you've said your piece.
我告诉你我怎么想的
Let me tell you what I think.
艇长
Captain...
我觉得你是开小差的士兵
I think you're a soldier that's gone A.W.O.L.
你是想偷渡回家  这个荒唐的说辞
You've hopped a ride home, and this cockeyed story
只是你想掩盖自己逃兵身份的疯狂企图
is some loony attempt to keep your cover as a civvie.
要么  你就是个间谍
That, or you're a spy.
判断是哪种就留给军事法庭吧
Deciding which? I'll leave that to the court martial.
我要单独跟此人谈谈
I need to speak with this man alone.
不行
Not a chance.
艇长  有些事
Captain, there are things,
关于此次任务的事  你不知道
things about this mission that you don't know.
登岸之前  这位闪电戈登
Flash Gordon here will remain under guard
-都由你来看守  -好的
- until we reach the shore. - Gladly.
万一我们上不了岸呢  万一他说对了呢
What if we don't reach shore? What if he's right?
德国军舰在这么西边的地方
The odds of a German attack from a surface ship,
袭击一艘海底潜艇的几率
this far west, hunting down a lone submarine?
艇长
Captain?
声纳探测到一艘海面船只在以固定方向向我艇靠近
Sonar's picked up a surface ship on a steady bearing, closing.
知道了
Understood.
哈里斯  回岗
Harris, back to your station.
吉拉尔迪  看好我们的客人
Giraldi, watch our guest.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
德国人  他们来找它了
The Germans, they've come for it.
黛尔芬  艇体上的咒符
Delphine, the warding on the hull? The sigil?
我从未见过
That's not like any I've seen.
-你确定没听错吗  -是  长官
- You're certain of the identification? - Yes, sir.
是36B德国驱逐舰
Uh, 36b German destroyer,
距离3000码  逐渐靠近  方位090
3,000 yards in closing. Bearing 0-9-0.
-无关人员撤出舰桥  -无关人员撤出舰桥
- Clear the bridge. - Clear the bridge!
我的导师是记录者
My mentor in the Men of Letters,
他死前把这个咒符教给了我
he taught me the symbol before he died.
世界职业棒球大赛  1944年  说
World Series, 1944. Go.
你是未来来的
You're from the future.
告诉我  谁赢了
Tell me, who won?
流浪者队
Um, the, uh, the Rangers.
The rangers?
他认为咒符能在航行途中保护我
He believed it would keep me and the artifact safe
-和文物  -流浪者队是谁啊
- on our journey... - Who are the Rangers?
不被超自然力量干扰
...from supernatural interference.
还有天使的干扰
And angelic interference.
-天使  那不是真的  -流浪者队是谁
- Angels? They are not real. - Who are the Rangers?
小子  我不关注棒球  好吗
Look, kid, I don't follow baseball, okay?
而且是的  天使是真的
Yeah, and angels are real.
事实上  我就是靠其中一位上了艇
In fact, one of them is my ride off this ship.
听我说  你用来抵挡魔法的咒符
Now look, the warding that you put up to block the magic,
一定也把他挡在了外面  我擦了一个
it must've blocked him, too. I cleared the one.
如果还有别的  那些也得擦掉
If there's any more, we gotta clear those, too.
否则我就困在这儿了
Otherwise, I'm stuck here.
那好吧  下任总统
Okay, then. The next president.
黛尔芬  你希望把武器
Delphine, you wanted the weapon
送去记录者的安全屋  是吧
to be at a Men of Letters safe house, right?
我就是从地堡来的
I'm from the bunker.
我就是这样知道怎么找你的
That's how I knew how to find you,
靠你和亨肖的通讯
from your communication with Henshaw.
如果你扫清障碍  我就能替你带回去
Now if you clear the way, I can get it there for you.
这就是你来的目的
And that's why you came,
保护那东西  那武器
to protect the object, the weapon?
你要不要回答我
You gonna answer my question?
艾森豪威尔  好吗  不对  是杜鲁门
Eisenhower, okay? No. Uh...Truman.
你能不能闭嘴了
Now would you please shut up?
不  这艘潜艇要沉没的
No. This sub is going down.
但盟军赢了
But the allies do win.
但同作为记录者我跟你说一句
But from Man of Letters to Man of Letters?
我正在未来打一场仗
I'm fighting a war in the future.
跟你的战争不同
It's not like your war.
这场战争很大  像圣经  世界末日那样大
It's big. Biblical, end-is-nigh big.
我需要你的武器获胜
And I need your weapon to win.
这就是我来的目的
That is why I came.
我们都死了吗
But we all die?
我  这女孩  和其余艇员
Me, the girl, the rest of the crew?
我只是想理清你的故事
I'm just trying to get your story clear.
是的
Yes.
听我说  我知道这要求很过分
Look, I know it's a lot to ask,
尤其我还是个陌生人
especially from a complete stranger.
你不是陌生人
You're not a stranger.
"同作为记录者"
"Man of Letters to Man of Letters."
我信任你
I trust you.
舱口已锁
Hatch secure.
航向变更至270  下潜至60英尺
Alter course to 2-7-0. Take us down to 60 feet.
航向变更至270
Alter course to 2-7-0!
-变更航向至270  -开前接口
- Altering course to 2-7-0. - Open front port.
-下潜  下潜  -下潜
- Dive, dive, dive! - Dive! Dive!
等等  我好像有发现
Wait a second. I think I have something.
"召集咒"
"The spell of gathering."
这个咒语是用来
It's an incantation used
"集中天上生灵"  天使  "的力量
to "focus the power of celestial beings"... angels...
以抵御各种形式的驱逐"
"against all drawn forms of evasion."
这个咒语是用来
This spell was designed
清除一切神秘防御的
to clear all mystical or occult blockages.
这是很理论化的魔法
I mean, this is highly theoretical magic.
从未有人用过
It's never been used before,
但听上去好使
but it sounds like it could work.
需要什么配料吗
Do you have the ingredients?
只差一样
All but one.
怪不得从未有人用过
That's why it's never been used before.
需要一名大天使的力量
It requires the power of an archangel.
萨姆  我们不妨一试
Well, Sam, we may as well try.
我们没时间尝试希望不大的东西  小卡
We don't have time for long shots, Cass.
就算你在全盛时期也不够强大
Even at full power, you're not strong enough.
那就是上帝之手吗
That's the Hand of God?
看上去没什么特别
Doesn't look like much.
是啊
No, I suppose it doesn't.
完整的时候肯定更震撼
It must have been more impressive in its complete form.
是约柜
The Ark of the Covenant.
这么《夺宝奇兵》啊  真是...
Oh, so full-on "raiders." That's...
好吧
Okay.
别赤手碰
Don't touch it bare-handed.
它威力无边而且不稳定
Its power is potent and unstable.
凡人直接长时间接触会要命的
No mortal can survive long with direct contact.
我去擦掉咒符
I'll remove the warding.
就回来
I'll be back.
我保证
Promise.
你可不行
Definitely not you.
好吧
Okay.
什么时候
When?
什么什么时候
When what?
我们什么时候胜利
When do we win?
还有几个月  几年  几十年
Months, years, decades?
我还有很多亲人朋友在其他舰上
Got a lot of friends and family on other ships,
在其他部队
in other branches.
我想知道他们能不能活下来
I want to know what their chances are.
还有好几年
Years.
1945年
1945.
你相信我吗
You believe me?
我读过很多闪电戈登的故事
I read a lot of Flash Gordon.
1500码  我们甩不掉他们
1,500 yards. We are not shaking him.
准备作战
Battle stations.
长官  恕我直言
Sir, respectfully,
我们的命令是回国  不是交战
our orders were to go home, not engage.
副艇长  别逼我重复命令
X.O., do not make me repeat myself.
-准备作战  -是  长官
- Battle stations! - Aye, aye, sir!
一级战备  各就各位
General quarters, battle stations.
General quarters, man your battle stations.
-所有人  各就各位  -好了  行动
- All hands, man your battle stations. - Okay, let's go!
行动起来  快点
Let's go, boys! Let's go! Come on! Come on!
好了  行动起来
Go! Okay! Okay!
快走  快走  快点
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
别停下  快点
Keep it going! Keep it going! Go.
-叫你们动起来呢  -快走
- He said get a move on! - Get a move on!
快走  所有人各就位
Get to it! Get to it! Everyone in positions!
准备给8号弹膛装弹
Stand by to load tube number 8.
装填尾部鱼雷
Load aft torpedoes.
-装填尾部鱼雷  -装填尾部鱼雷
- Load aft torpedoes. - Load aft torpedoes.
哈里斯  把后门打开
Harris, open the rear door.
-开门  -可以了
- Opening door. - Go! Clear!
小心  慢慢来
Easy. Ease it down.
-锁好了  -放水
- We're secured! - Flood the tube.
放水
Flooding.
准备开火
Ready to fire.
距离300码  仍在靠近
800 yards and closing.
-鱼雷装填完毕  -瞄准船首
- Torpedoes loaded. - Line us up for a bow shot.
-瞄准船首  -瞄准船首
- Line up for a bow shot. - Lining up for a bow shot.
-目标锁定  -就位  可以开火
- Locked. - In position, ready to fire.
艇长  我找不到他了
Captain, uh, I-I've lost his position.
-什么  -他不见了
- What? - He's gone.
一艘距离800码
How is it possible
三千吨的军舰怎么可能凭空消失
to lose a 3,000-ton warship from 800 yards?
找到他
Find him!
-30码  长官  就在我们上方  -怎么会
- 30 yards, sir! He's right on top of us! - How?!
下潜
Flood negative!
潜至最低深度  准备无声前进
Take us down to max depth and rig for silent running!
无声前进
Silent running!
怎么回事
What's happening?
到达300码深度了  长官
Leveling out at 300, sir.
-杀了我  -等一下
- Kill me. - Wait.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
杀了我
Kill me.
水声
Splashes.
深水炸弹
Depth charge.
我没必要杀你  明白吗
I don't have to kill you, okay?
切一刀就行
I can just cut it. It'll work.
这个不行
Not with this.
这咒语与我的血液  我的心脏相连
It's spell-bound... to my blood, my heart.
它的魔力随我生  跟我死
Its power lives and dies with me.
动手吧
Do it.
见习艇员受伤  我们需要医生
Midshipman down! We need a medic!
小卡  那是什么
Cass, what is that?
那个召集咒语的材料
It's your spell of gathering.
你疯了吗
Are you nuts?
你不够强壮  小卡  你会受伤的
You're not strong enough, Cass. You could get hurt.
你找到更好的办法了吗
You find a better option?
没有
Well...No,
但除非大大提升你的天使法力
but without a serious boost to your angel power,
咒语根本不会起效
that spell won't even work.
我的力量或许会出乎你的意料
My strength may surprise you.
等一下
Wait a second.
我记得鲍比说过
I remember Bobby told me,
你需要能量将我们从过去带回来时
when you needed strength to retrieve us from the past,
你利用了他
you used him to power up.
你用了他的灵魂  对吗
You... you touched his soul. Right?
没错
That's right. I did that.
但那过程有致命危险
But that... that, uh, procedure it can be fatal.
用我的灵魂
Use my soul.
也许这样你就有足够能量用那个咒语了
That way, maybe you'll have enough power to wield the spell.
没那个必要
That isn't necessary.
这风险值得冒
It's worth the risk.
小卡  迪恩需要我们
Cass, Dean needs our help.
我信任你
I trust you.
怎么了
What?
我根本不需要你了
Oh, it's ju-- I don't... I don't need you anymore.
和阿玛拉有联系的是迪恩
I mean, Dean's the one with the link to Amara.
我为什么要放过你
Why have I been trying to spare you?
可能是因为
I mean, maybe it's because
你就像那个总在舞会上拒绝我邀请的妹子吧
you're like the girl who kept turning me down at the prom.
我会触碰你的灵魂
I will touch your soul,
既然你这么热切
just because you asked so nicely.
然后我就用你那咒语  突破咒符
and I'll use your spell to blast through the warding
找回迪恩和上帝之手
and retrieve Dean and the, uh...Hand of God.
等迪恩回来时
And then when Dean comes back
会发现你血溅三尺
and he finds this place decorated with your guts,
我就告诉他实情  萨姆
I will tell him the truth, Sam.
我会说  迪恩
I'll just say, "Dean"...
迪恩
Dean...
他明知道有危险
He knew the risks.
可就是非要那么做
He wouldn't take 'no' for an answer."
你是路西法
Lucifer.
正是
In the flesh.
你好啊  卡西迪奥
Hello, Castiel.
医生
Medic!
快
Come on!
损坏报告
Damage report?
电池室被淹  艇体受损
Battery room is flooded. Hull's breached.
我们要淹死了
We're dead in the water.
敌舰锁定在了我们上方
Ship's locked in position above us.
呼叫美方潜艇
American submarine.
艇长
Captain...
德国人在发送一条信息
The Germans are sending a message.
呼叫美方潜艇
American submarine.
长官  不是给你的
Sir, it's not for you.
小心头
Watch your head.
接通吧
Go ahead.
你好呀  亲爱的
Hello, mein liebchen.
不可能  我杀死了你
It is not possible. I killed you.
一个小建议  黛尔芬
A little advice, Delphine.
如果你想让一名修黎社的朋友死透
If you want a friend of the Thule to stay dead,
得把尸体烧了
burn the body.
给艇长递句话
A word for the Captain.
你也许已经意识到了  你所应对的战舰
You may have noticed you are up against a warship
和船员拥有...
and a crew possessing,
超凡的能力
let us say, extraordinary abilities.
而你们已经受了不可挽回的损伤
And you have taken damage that you cannot recover from.
所以我给你们一个选择...
So I offer you a choice...
马上上浮  交出那个女孩和她的货物
Surface now, relinquish the girl and her cargo,
我就保证让你和你的人
and I can assure you and your men
享受最高级别的战俘待遇
the highest of P.O.W. treatment.
或者你可以保护她
Or you can protect her,
那么我们将投放深水炸弹让你
and we will depth charge you and your boat
和你的潜艇沉入海底
right into the seabed
然后我们再自己去取回货物
and recover the cargo ourselves.
给你三分钟时间投降
You have three minutes to surrender.
我不指望你们理解  但这件货物
I don't expect you to understand, but this cargo,
不能落到德国人手上
the Germans can't have it.
你们得相信我
You need to believe me.
我们收到的命令是保护你和你的货物
Our orders were to protect you and your cargo.
我们不会考虑投降的
We wouldn't even consider a surrender.
你最好重新考虑一下
You had better reconsider.
杀了我是你离开这艘潜艇的唯一办法
Killing me is your only way off this ship.
也许不是
Maybe not.
教我如何使用它
Teach me how to use it.
这可是上帝之力
It's the power of God.
也许我能用它来救你  救这艘潜水艇
Maybe I can use it to save you, save the sub.
-那你的战争怎么办  -现在我想帮助你
- And your war? - I want to help you now.
还有两分钟  艇长
Two minutes, Captain.
你救下这艘潜艇
You save the ship,
帮我们到达水面  然后呢
get us to the surface, and then what?
上帝之力会毁了你
The power of God will consume you,
而你不过是将这件武器
and you'll have merely brought the weapon
送到了纳粹门前
closer to the Nazis' grasp.
我们本来就得死
We are supposed to die.
让我们死得其所吧
Let us do it with a purpose.
你能保持潜艇稳定行驶多久
How long can you keep the boat steady?
不会很久  一旦他们恢复攻击...
Not long. And once they resume their attack...
尽量帮我争取时间
Give me every second you can.
黛尔芬  你在干什么
Delphine, what are you doing?
-还剩一分钟  -我要帮你回家
- One minute. - I'm going to get you home.
还要帮你和你的人
And I'm going to get you and your men
打沉你们第一艘德国军舰
your first German ship.
不不  萨姆
No, no. Sam.
萨姆  是我
Sam, it's me.
小卡  为什么
Cass? Why?
我希望在这场战斗中出一份力
I wanted to be of service to the fight.
只有路西法能打败她
And only Lucifer can beat her.
你自己选择的吗
You chose this?
你得反抗  小卡  现在就驱逐他
You have to fight, Cass. Eject him now!
我做不到
I can't.
为了不让他杀你  我已经用上了全部力量
It's taking all my strength to keep him from killing you.
而且我们需要他
And besides, we need him.
不  小卡  我们不需要
No, Cass, we don't.
我们会找到别的办法阻止阿玛拉
We'll find another way to stop Amara.
我们需要他救出迪恩
We need him to save Dean.
你无法完成穿越
You can't time travel.
只有路西法可以
Only Lucifer can.
你穿回去的速度有多快
How fast is your ride back?
-很快  -很好
- Fast. - Good.
到时候了
It's time!
上帝保佑我们
God help us all.
切断仪表盘
Isolate that panel!
什么情况
What is this?!
控制室起火了
Fire in the control room!
鱼雷进水了  我们需要...
Torpedoes are taking water! We need...
迪恩
Dean.
他不是小卡
That's not Cass!
被发现了
Cat's out.
真是解脱了
I feel a burden lifted.
隐瞒身份什么的
You know, this whole "deep cover" thing,
实在是有欠考虑
it just wasn't... it wasn't terribly well thought out.
穿着小卡的这身皮囊
Donning this...this Cass mask?
这副犹如天使便秘一般的臭脸
This grim face of angelic constipation?
真是太...
Just ugh...
还有和你们俩搭伙...
And then teaming up with you two? I mean...
你们作为我的死敌就够烦人了
I thought you boys were insufferable as mortal enemies.
但和你们合作
but working with you?
简直是要我的命
Ugh. That's the soul crusher.
干吗苦着脸  孩子们
Why the faces, boys?
你们该欢呼雀跃  我们有共同的敌人
You should be cheering. We have a common enemy.
有了这个  她就不成问题了
With this, she will be no problem.
我是说...
I mean...
到时我肯定已经杀了你俩了  不过...
I will have killed you both by then, but still...
拜托
come on.
不
No.
No!
没能量了
It's kicked.
好吧
Well...
谁能想到上帝之手
Who'd have thought the hand of God
只能打一炮
would turn out to be a one-hitter?
那么
So...
小卡
Cass.
嗯
Yeah.
我们怎么办
Yeah, what do we do?
还能做什么
What else?
我们追踪路西法
We hunt Lucifer,
抓住那个混蛋  救回小卡
trap the bastard, and save Cass.
如我所说
Like I said,
现在虽是路西法在掌控
Lucifer may be in control now,
但小卡也许不会自愿回来
but Cass may not come back willingly.
-这是他的选择  -不
- I mean, he chose it. - No.
不  不可能
No, not possible.
你今天是怎么过来的  你都做了什么
So how'd you get through today? I mean, what did you do?
什么都没做
Nothing.
萨姆  他们
Sam, they...
我只是一个旁观者
I was just a witness.
你想聊聊吗
Do you want to talk about it?
不想
No.
不  改天再说吧
No. Story for another day.
那个...
Hey, the, uh...
击沉蓝鳍号的德国军舰
The German ship that sank the Bluefin,
后来怎么样了
what happened to it?
沉了
It went down.
和潜艇不同  军舰的残骸被找到了
Unlike the sub, its wreckage was found.
有个巨大的洞
Um, there was a giant hole
把整个船身都撕开了
that'd been ripped through the entire thing.
一定是有什么撞到了油箱  爆炸了
Something must have hit the fuel tanks and exploded.
战舰起火  沉了
But it burned. Sank.